<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Routines</string>

    <string name="splash_text">Routines</string>
    <!-- onboarding -->
    <string name="onboard_welcome_title_00">Welcome!</string>
    <string name="onboard_welcome_01">\nYou installed Routines because:\n\n\n\n
     &#9999; You want to set new or change your habits \n
     &#9999; You want to change the pace of your life.\n
     &#9999; You want to drive a change within yourself.\n
        &#9999; Perhaps you are just curious about yourself.\n\n\n
        Is this you?\n</string>
    <string name="onboard_welcome_02">
        Great! Lets get started by establishing the most important
    task of the day:\n\n  &lt;b&gt;The Morning Planner.&lt;\/b&gt;\n\n

         Are you ready?
    </string>

    <string name="onboard_title_03">Planing</string>

    <string name="onboard_title_05">Reflecting</string>
    <string name="onboard_title_finish">Done!</string>
    <string name="onboard_welcome_03">

        “An intelligent plan is the first step to success. The man who plans knows where he is going, knows what progress he is making and has a pretty good idea when he will arrive.”
– Basil S. Walsh\n\n\nPlanning your day is the most important habit to develop because it is a an opportunity for you to measure the effectiveness of all of your other habits as well as the
        ability to develop new habits. In other words, if you are having difficulty establishing this morning habit, there is a very high probability that you will have difficulty changing
        other habits as well. To be effective you must develop this habit first. Lets practise once by checking your Notifications.

    </string>
    <string name="onboard_welcome_04">
        Every morning Routines will remind you to plan your day. It will pre-schedule tasks as well as provide options for you to
        approve, modify, edit, re-order and remove tasks. These options are available to you at anytime. Remember that planning your day is
        the most important task of the day so if you are a stubborn person when it comes to Notifications, it is a wise choice to make this notification persistent.\n\n
        Are you Stubborn?

    </string>

    <string name="onboard_done_description">

        "Drop by drop the cup is slowly filled. Don't strive for perfection. Have patience and enjoy the process and soon you will find yourself a master without even trying."
        \n\n\n
        Your task for today is ready! Be sure to tick it off before you sleep!

    </string>

    <string name="onboard_description_5">

        The last thing to do is to pick a time on which to reflect on your achievements of the day.
        This will help you appreciate how amazing you already are, which is vital in the process
        of self-discovery. Pick a time to reflect. It should ideally be right before bed.

    </string>

    <string name="onboard_pick_time">Pick Time</string>
    <string name="onboard_close">On with my day</string>

    <string name="onboard_choice_01_04">I\'m Stubborn</string>
    <string name="onboard_choice_02_04">I prefer to dismiss Notifications</string>
    <string name="onboard_welcome_06"></string>

    <string name="onboard_continue">Yes</string>

    <string name="onboard_welcome_10"></string>

    <string name="onboard_welcome_11">Are you ready? </string>
    <string name="onboard_ready">I\'m ready</string>

    <string name="onboard_wake_up_text">I wake up at:</string>
    <string name="onboard_sleep_text">I sleep at:</string>
    <string name="onboard_default_text">Pick:</string>
    <string name="onboard_seed">"Great! Your first daily task, the most important task, is to plan your day. Let's do a test run. "</string>
    <string name="info_oops_string">We made an oopsy! Try again?</string>
    <string name="info_argument_key">info_text</string>

    <!-- onboard pillars -->

    <string name="pillars_title">The Pillars of Life</string>

    <string name="pillars_description"> As you progress through the app, you should ideally balance out the Pillars of your Life. For now, choose one area of your life on which to improve
     upon. </string>

    <string name="pillar_suggestion_description">Here are some suggestions. You can always create your own by pressing "Add my own". Remember that
       these habits are aimed at improving your life. Specific tasks are more actionable and are easier to turn into habits </string>

    <string name="pillar_mental">Mental</string>
    <string name="pillar_physical">Physical</string>
    <string name="pillar_relationships">Relationships</string>
    <string name="pillar_recreational">Play</string>
    <string name="pillar_work">Work Life</string>
    <string name="pillar_other">Other</string>
    <string name="task_add">Add My Own </string>

</resources>

